question_data = [
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The Neanderthals were a direct ancestor of modern humans.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "The Ceratosaurus, a dinosaur known for having a horn on the top "
                                                  "of its nose, is also known to be a decendent of the "
                                                  "Tyrannosaurus Rex.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "FLAC stands for Free Lossless Audio Condenser", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "The first televised presidential debate was between "
                                                  "Jimmy Carter and Gerald Ford.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Coca-Cola original colour was green.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "Scottish producer Calvin Harris is from the town of "
                                                  "Dumfries, Scotland.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Team Fortress, the Bills Hat is a reference to the game Dota.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "TF2: The Heavy voice actor, Gary Schwartz, voices the Demoman as well ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The Hundred Years War was fought for more than a hundred years.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "Norway has a larger land area than Sweden.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Klingons once had a period of Democracy in their history, "
                 "they referred to it as the Dark Times.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Android versions are named in alphabetical order.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The ADAM collecters in the Bioshock series are known as Little Sisters.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "Pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis is a "
                                                   "synonym for the disease known as silicosis.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "You can square root a negative number with an imaginary number &quot;i&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Musical artist, Future, collaborated with Kendrick Lamar for the song: &quot;Mask Off&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The movie Tron received an Oscar nomination for Best Visual Effects.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Night on Bald Mountain was one of the musical pieces featured in "
                 "Disney 1940s film Fantasia.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Snagglepuss was part of the Yogi Yahooies in the 1977 show Scooby All-Star Laff-a-Lympics.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The most frequent subconscious activity repeated by the human body is blinking.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
